http://www.macarthurchurch.org/privacy.html

PRIVACY POLICY
At the MacArthur Park Church of Christ, we are committed to protecting your privacy. Any information that we collect is used to provide the best possible experience for visitors. By using a web site maintained by the MacArthur Park Church of Christ, you agree to the terms set forth below. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this website.A. Privacy PolicyMacArthur Park Church of Christ reviews our Privacy Policy periodically, and we reserve the right, at our discretion, to modify or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. This page should be reviewed from time to time, so that you can be aware of any changes. This Privacy Policy applies to all websites produced and operated by the MacArthur Park Church of Christ. If you want to communicate with us about our Privacy Policy, email us at administrator@macarthurchurch.org  or write us at: the MacArthur Park Church of Christ1907 NE Loop 410, San Antonio, Texas 78217B. Collection & UseMacArthur Park Church of Christ recognizes the privacy concerns of users of our websites on the Internet and the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected from them. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information, such as a visitor’s name, address, email address, telephone number, or credit card information is automatically collected on our websites. Such information is collected only when it is knowingly and voluntarily submitted, and MacArthur Park Church of Christ uses such information only for the purpose for which it was submitted, unless we disclose other uses in this policy or at the time of collection.We maintain reasonable and appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of such information in our possession. MacArthur Park Church of Christ does not sell personally identifiable information to third parties. MacArthur Park Church of Christ will not disclose, sell, trade, or rent personal information it collects to outside parties. We reserve the right to monitor visitor traffic patterns and website usage to help us develop the design and layout of our websites to enhance your online experience.C. SecurityOur technology partners use industry-leading Internet security technology and practices. They use secure server software (SSL) that encrypts the information you input before you send it to us. All of the data is protected against unauthorized access.D. CookiesCookies are small bits of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive to enable us to do a number of things to make your visit and future visits more enjoyable. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to prevent that. Users should consult their browser help files for instructions on how to refuse cookies. Visitors may also receive cookies from third parties, but MacArthur Park Church of Christ cannot control the content of those cookies.E. PromotionsMacArthur Park Church of Christ may run promotions on our websites that require submission of personally identifiable information by participants. MacArthur Park Church of Christ may use the information collected in the aggregate so we can determine, for example, how many visitors to our website participated in the promotion. Promotions are subject to change without notice.F. LinksOur websites may be linked to or from other websites that are not operated by MacArthur Park Church of Christ. MacArthur Park Church of Christ is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these third-party websites. G. Technology ProvidersElevation Church partners with several technology providers in order to deliver the best possible online experience to visitors. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the Privacy Policies of these providers by following the links below:www.smartsheet.comwww.easytithe.comDisclaimer of Liability:In preparation of this site, every effort has been made to offer the most current, correct, and clearly expressed information possible. Nevertheless, inadvertent errors in information may occur, and information may become dated. In particular, but without limiting anything stated herein, MacArthur Park Church of Christ disclaims any responsibility for typographical errors and accuracy or timeliness of the information that may be contained on MacArthur Park Church of Christ’s websites. MacArthur Park Church of Christ  also reserves the right to make changes at any time without notice. If misleading, inaccurate or otherwise inappropriate information is brought to our attention, a reasonable effort will be made to fix or remove it. Please contact administrator@macarthurchurch.org with any concerns.Links to Third Party Websites:The documents on this website may serve to provide access to the World Wide Web. Because the MacArthur Park Church of Christ website connects to the Internet, once you leave the MacArthur Park Church of Christ website, MacArthur Park Church of Christ cannot control the information you access. MacArthur Park Church of Christ links to external websites in the hope that users will find reference material on related subjects. MacArthur Park Church of Christ does not control those sites and is not responsible for the content included in them, including without limitation, any subsequent links contained within a linked site, or any changes or updates to a linked site. Each individual site has its own set of policies about what information is appropriate for public access. MacArthur Park Church of Christ is not responsible for any information or material located at any site other than official MacArthur Park Church of Christ websites.Disclaimer of Reliability:MacArthur Park Church of Christ makes no representations or warranties regarding the condition or functionality of this website, its suitability for use, or that this web service will be uninterrupted or error-free.Disclaimer of Damages:By using an MacArthur Park Church of Christ website, you assume all risks associated with the use of the site, including any risk to your computer, software or data being damaged by any virus, software, or any other file that might be transmitted or activated via an MacArthur Park Church of Christ website or your access to it. MacArthur Park Church of Christ shall not be liable for any damages of any kind (general, special, incidental or consequential damages, including, without limitation, lost revenues or lost profits) resulting from the use or misuse of the information contained in an MacArthur Park Church of Christ website.Copyrights and Trademarks:Copyright (c) 2018 MacArthur Park Church of Christ, Inc All Rights ReservedAll material on this website is copyrighted by MacArthur Park Church of Christ, except for some material that is copyrighted by others and used here by permission. Copyrighted material may not be copied, reproduced or otherwise used for commercial purposes without the written permission of the copyright holder. This site also contains some trademarks, which may not be appropriated by persons other than the trademark owner and may not be used contrary to trademark law. If you wish to request permission to use materials in a manner otherwise prohibited herein, please send an email to: administrator@macarthurchurch.org or contact us via telephone at (210)824-7301. MacArthur Park Church of Christ1907 NE Loop 410San Antonio, Texas 78217210.824.7301adminstrator@macarthurchurch.orgwww.macarthurchurch.orgwww.macyouth.orgwww.mackidz.org
Current WORSHIP schedule (DuRING PANDEMIC):Sundays: 9:00 a.m.    in- person worship  (please pre-register)10:30 a.m.  IN-PERSON WORSHIP (PLEASE PRE-REGISTER)10:30 A.M.  LIVE-STREAM WORSHIP
1907 NE Loop 410San Antonio, Texas 78217210.824.7301© 2020 MacArthur Park Church of ChristPrivacy Policy
